

Falmouth, Cornwall, United Kingdom

■ harry.bd11@gmail.com | HDonovan96 | MeachAbyss

Summary

I am an avid programmer and competent and passionate producer, with a strong knowledge of version control using Git, agile methodology, and an excitement for facing new, interesting challenges. I have lead teams which have published to both Itch and Steam, always with a focus on maintaining healthy and flexible working practices. My ideal position would be junior producer role, with a strong focus on growing my skills and experience so I could progress to a more senior position.

Skills

- · Project Management: Agile, Scrum, Sprint Planning, Trello
- · Version Control: Git
- · Game Engines: Unity, Unreal Engine 4
- Languages: C#, C++, Latex

Education

Falmouth University

BSc Computing For Games

Falmouth, United Kingdom

Sept. 2019 - June 2022

Published Games

Carma - Producer & Team Lead

Unity 2019.4

SELF PUBLISHED TO STEAM (HTTPS://STORE.STEAMPOWERED.COM/APP/1603990/CARMA/)

Published June 2021

- · Worked with a multidisciplinary team to bring Carma from concept to published game
- Planned sprints and development milestones using Agile
- Removed blockers and streamlined development pipelines
- · Focused on maintaining team health and reinforcing healthy working practices
- · Set up Steam store and kept builds updated

Yvaga Station - Team Lead & Programmer

Unity 2018.4

SELF PUBLISHED TO ITCH.IO (HTTPS://DAYLUKE.ITCH.IO/YVAGA-STATION)

Published May 2020

- Presented a concept pitch to in order to continue development past prototype stage
- Implemented asymmetric multiplayer game using PUN2 package for networking
- Designed and implemented a modular custom movement system to expand on the options available to the player

Work Experience _____

GLASS NOMAD GAMES

FXPLUS

Director Falmouth, Cornwall

• Started a company to publish video games my team and I were developing

• Handled registration and set up with services such as Steam

Senior Ambassador

Falmouth, Cornwall

March 2021 - Current

June 2020 - Current

- · Promoted from Student Ambassador
- Increased responsibility for the smooth running of events
- Manages the distribution of Student Ambassadors during events
- · Relied on to handle any complications or problems that arise during an event

Programming Projects

Boids Simulation

Unity 2019.4

February 2021 - May 2021

HTTPS://GITHUB.COM/HDONOVAN96/BOIDSSIMULATION

- Investigated boids and optimisation methods
- Implemented multithreading and spatial partitioning
- Pivoted to data-oriented rather than object-oriented implementation for performance

HARRY DONOVAN · RÉSUMÉ JUNE 11, 2021